JORGE KEAN DE LOS REYES

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

PROFILE

I am a full stack software engineer with 10 years of experience in the .NET technology stack. Have a proven ability to efficiently work with a diverse team, and a strong background in object-oriented programming. I am also conducting internal training on several topics such as SQL, ASP.NET MVC, and AngularJS.

https://jorgekean.github.io/jkn-profile/

CONTACT

- **2** 0998 565 5106
- ✓ jkn379@gmail.com
- Puting Bato East, Calaca, Batangas, Philippines

SKILLS & TOOLS

- ASP.NET
- C#
- MS SQL
- Visual Studio
- Entity Framework (ORM)
- Selenium (Browser Automation)
- SSRS
- HTML, JavaScript, CSS
- JQuery, AngularJS, ReactJS
- NPM, NodeJS
- Azure

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Cavite State University 2008 - 2012

EXPERIENCE

SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Willis Towers Watson Global Business Services
Oct 2016 - Present

- Implements and supports the Heath and Benefits System of US clients
- Develop internal applications for the organization to make their work more efficient
- Perform code reviews to junior developers
- Interact with the client teams to discuss the requirements and timeline of the projects.

TECHNICAL SPECIALIST

Provoke Solutions Makati Inc.

March 2016 - Sept 2016

- Developed an API to be consumed by a mobile app
- Developed enhancements on clients' websites
- Earned Microsoft Certified Solutions Developer (MCSD) certification

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Systems and Software Consulting Group Inc.

Jan 2013 - March 2016

- Supports the monitoring and inventory management system
- · Develop financial system for local clients